Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XLIV is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
Series XLV is arranged in 32 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XLIV. AMERICAN FEDERATION OF LABOR, RAILWAY EMPLOYEES DEPARTMENT
  - Sub-Series 290-0. American Federation of Labor, Railway Employees Department
    - General, 1949-1956. (Box 471, Folder 8)
      1949-56..
- Series XLV. GRAND LODGE OFFICERS
  - Sub-Series 297-1. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Activities. General Representatives, 1928 (Box 471, Folder 9)
    - Activities. General Representatives, 1927 (Box 471, Folder 10)
    - Activities. General Representatives, 1925-1926 (Box 471, Folder 11)
    - Activities. General Representatives, 1925 (Box 471, Folder 12)
    - Activities. General Representatives, 1923 (Box 471, Folder 13)
    - Activities. General Representatives, 1921-1922 (Box 471, Folder 14)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. McCarthy, R.J., 1959-1963 (Box 472, Folder 1)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. McCarthy, R.J., 1953-1958 (Box 472, Folder 2)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. McCarthy, R.J., 1947-1952 (Box 472, Folder 3)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. Ripp, H.J., 1951-1959 (Box 472, Folder 4)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. Bruen, F., 1935-1956 (Box 472, Folder 5)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Organizers. General; Abbott, J.R.; Aldrich, R.G.; Arnold, A.M.; Boaz, V.L.; Bonham, R.S.; Braggins, W.F.; Butler, J.J., 1933-1949 (Box 472, Folder 6)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Organizers. Carr, M.S.; Clancey, J.; Coleman, A.M.; Constable, B.R.; Cooper, S.H.; Crawford, W.M.; Davies, H.V.; Davis, C.G.; Edwards, P.G.; Eklund, E.G.; Gaynor, A.F.; Gifford, B.E.; Gilbert, J.I.; Grosser, F.W.; Harvey, A.P.; Has, 1933-1949 (Box 472, Folder 7)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Organizers. Mose, A., 1947-1956 (Box 472, Folder 8)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Organizers. Davis, R.E., 1950-1955 (Box 472, Folder 9)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Organizers. Larson, A.E.; Lawler, J.F.; Leckie, D.; McCall, J.W.; McGhee, A.J.; McGuigan, J.C.; McIlvaine, J.H.; MacGregor, R.; Preston, N.L.; Rapoport, W.; Ratcliffe, J.J.; Rogers, E.; Rogers, H.; Ryan, W.D.; Speer, J.; St. John, 1933-1949 (Box 472, Folder 10)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Organizers. Goodwin, H.L., 1946-1960 (Box 472, Folder 11)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Organizers. Harrison, H.C., 1954-1956 (Box 472, Folder 12)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Organizers. Spencer, J.P., 1954-1955 (Box 472, Folder 13)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Organizers. Sylvester, L.H., 1953-1955 (Box 472, Folder 14)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. Dyer, J.L., 1947-1950 (Box 472, Folder 15)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. O'Connell, J.J., 1947-1949 (Box 472, Folder 16)
    - Activities. General Representatives., 1932 (Box 472, Folder 17)
    - Activities. General Representatives., 1931 (Box 472, Folder 18)
    - Activities. General Representatives., 1930 (Box 472, Folder 19)
    - Activities. General Representatives., 1929 (Box 472, Folder 20)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. General, 1948-1959 (Box 473, Folder 1)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Babcock, R.A., 1958 (Box 473, Folder 2)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Babcock, R.A., 1951-1958 (Box 473, Folder 3)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Barber, H., 1958-1959 (Box 473, Folder 4)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Barber, H., 1951-1957 (Box 473, Folder 5)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Campbell, D.K., 1948-1957 (Box 473, Folder 6)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Clancy, P.T., 1947-1957 (Box 473, Folder 7)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Clark, J.O., 1950-1956 (Box 473, Folder 8)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Clark, J.O., 1963-1966 (Box 473, Folder 9)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Cobean, J.E., 1961-1968 (Box 473, Folder 10)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Organizers and Representatives. Courtney, E., 1955-1957 (Box 473, Folder 11)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. Crawford, W.M., 1958-1962 (Box 473, Folder 12)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. Crawford, W.M., 1948-1957 (Box 473, Folder 13)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. Davie, A.R., 1965 (Box 473, Folder 14)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. Day, P.F., 1958-1964 (Box 473, Folder 15)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. Day, P.F., 1953-1957 (Box 473, Folder 16)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. Dennis, C.L., 1955 (Box 473, Folder 17)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. Dickinson, W.J., 1956-1957 (Box 473, Folder 18)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. Dunaway, H.P., 1960 (Box 473, Folder 19)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. Erickson, L.M., 1958-1966 (Box 473, Folder 20)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. Erickson, L.M., 1945-1957 (Box 473, Folder 21)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. Ford, J.R., 1963-1965 (Box 473, Folder 22)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. Ford, J.R., 1962-1963 (Box 473, Folder 23)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Gibson, G.W., 1958-1963 (Box 473, Folder 24)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Gibson, G.W., 1946-1957 (Box 473, Folder 25)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Giroux, C., 1950-1954 (Box 473, Folder 26)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Giroux, C., 1958-1964 (Box 473, Folder 27)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Grimes, T.D., 1958-1964 (Box 473, Folder 28)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Grimes, T.D., 1953-1957 (Box 473, Folder 29)
      March 1953-57.
    - Activities. Special Representatives. Harper, H.W., 1949-1950 (Box 473, Folder 30)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Hartley, J.W., 1963-1964 (Box 473, Folder 31)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. Holmes, J.O., 1962-1963 (Box 473, Folder 32)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Kelly, E.F., 1958-1960 (Box 473, Folder 33)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Lanza, E.A., 1958-1967 (Box 473, Folder 34)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Lanza, E.A., 1937-1957 (Box 473, Folder 35)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. McCarthy, F.E., 1948-1957 (Box 473, Folder 36)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. McKinney, L., 1940-1957 (Box 473, Folder 37)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Mayberry, R., 1947-1957 (Box 473, Folder 38)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. Miller, C.E., 1962 (Box 473, Folder 39)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. Moore, C.B., 1947 (Box 473, Folder 40)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Mose, A., 1960-1964 (Box 473, Folder 41)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Murphy, W.B., 1958-1959 (Box 473, Folder 42)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Murphy, W.B., 1951-1957 (Box 473, Folder 43)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. O'Connell, J.J., 1947-1955 (Box 473, Folder 44)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Quinn, E.G., 1965 (Box 473, Folder 45)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Roers, E.L., 1947-1957 (Box 473, Folder 46)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. Reynolds, K.D., 1937-1963 (Box 474, Folder 1)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Sommerfield, C.P., 1947-1957 (Box 474, Folder 2)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Spencer, J.P., 1933-1955 (Box 474, Folder 3)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Summerville, F.J., 1947-1957 (Box 474, Folder 4)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Sylvester, L.H., 1956-1958 (Box 474, Folder 5)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Tait, W.A., 1958-1961 (Box 474, Folder 6)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Tait, W.A., 1935-1957 (Box 474, Folder 7)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Turner, W.J., 1946-1957 (Box 474, Folder 8)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Tuttle, H.L., 1946-1957 (Box 474, Folder 9)
    - Activities. Grand Lodge Representatives and Organizers. Williams, G., 1959-1960 (Box 474, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 297-2. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Dennis, C.L. Subject: "Appeal: Menzner, W.W.", 1961-1963 (Box 474, Folder 11)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Atkinson, G.R., 1962-1963 (Box 474, Folder 12)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Dennis, C.L., 1957-1963 (Box 474, Folder 13)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Bearden, J.D., 1959-1962 (Box 474, Folder 14)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Downard, E.F., 1963-1967 (Box 474, Folder 15)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Dyer, J.L., 1964 (Box 474, Folder 16)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Gibbons, G.M., 1955-1957 (Box 474, Folder 17)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Goble, G.B., 1958-1963 (Box 474, Folder 18)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Goble, G.B., 1952-1957 (Box 474, Folder 19)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Goble, G.B., 1948-1951 (Box 474, Folder 20)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Goble, G.B., 1935-1947 (Box 474, Folder 21)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Hall, F.H., 1940-1962 (Box 474, Folder 22)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Jesse, J.P., 1951-1955 (Box 474, Folder 23)
      April 1951-55.
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Jesse, J.P., 1946-1951 (Box 474, Folder 24)
      1946-March 1951.
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Kief, C.E., 1959-1963 (Box 475, Folder 1)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Kinley, E.R., 1959 (Box 475, Folder 2)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Kinley, E.R., 1955-1957 (Box 475, Folder 3)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Lyons, H.R., 1954-1959 (Box 475, Folder 4)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Lyons, H.R., 1950-1953 (Box 475, Folder 5)
      November 1950-53.
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Lyons, H.R., 1947-1950 (Box 475, Folder 6)
      May 1947-October 1950.
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Lyons, H.R., 1935-1947 (Box 475, Folder 7)
      1935-April 1947.
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. McGovern, W.C., 1963-1967 (Box 475, Folder 8)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. McGovern, W.C., 1955-1962 (Box 475, Folder 9)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Morgan, R., 1945-1965 (Box 475, Folder 10)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Snedden, L.B., 1952-1957 (Box 475, Folder 11)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Snedden, L.B., 1948-1951 (Box 475, Folder 12)
      August 1948-51.
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Snedden, L.B., 1935-1948 (Box 475, Folder 13)
      1935-July 1948.
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Shaw, K.D., 1957-1963 (Box 475, Folder 14)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Sylvester, J.H., 1951-1959 (Box 475, Folder 15)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. Sylvester, J.H., 1935-1950 (Box 475, Folder 16)
    - Activities. Special Representatives. Moore, C.B., 1945-1947 (Box 475, Folder 17)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. General, 1933-1943 (Box 475, Folder 18)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. General, 1931 (Box 475, Folder 19)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. General, 1921-1922 (Box 476, Folder 1)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. General, 1921 (Box 476, Folder 2-3)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. General, 1922 (Box 476, Folder 4)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. General, 1926-1928 (Box 476, Folder 5)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents. General, 1923-1927 (Box 476, Folder 6)
    - Activities. Vice Grand Presidents, 1925 (Box 476, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 297-3. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Location Report Cards, 1929-1954 (Box 476, Folder 8)
    - Location Report Cards, 1926-1931 (Box 476, Folder 9)
    - Location Report Cards, 1921-1924 (Box 476, Folder 10)
    - Location Report Cards, 1922 (Box 476, Folder 11)
    - Location Report Cards, 1925 (Box 476, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 297-4. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Board of Directors, 1921-1924 (Box 476, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 297-5. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Monthly Reports. Vice Grand Presidents, 1935-1936 (Box 476, Folder 14)
    - Monthly Reports. Vice Grand Presidents. Eastty, G.W., 1931-1935 (Box 476, Folder 15)
    - Monthly Reports. Vice Grand Presidents. Chapman, H.J., 1931-1935 (Box 476, Folder 16)
    - Monthly Reports. Vice Grand Presidents, 1931 (Box 476, Folder 17)
    - Monthly Reports. Vice Grand Presidents. Riegel, L.W., 1935 (Box 476, Folder 18)
    - Monthly Reports. Vice Grand Presidents. Dunn, A.J., 1931-1935 (Box 476, Folder 19)
    - Monthly Reports. Vice Grand Presidents. McTigue, H., 1931-1935 (Box 476, Folder 20)
    - Monthly Reports. Vice Grand Presidents. Morgan, R., 1931-1935 (Box 476, Folder 21)
    - Monthly Reports. Vice Grand Presidents. Snedden, L. B., 1935-1936 (Box 476, Folder 22)
    - Monthly Reports. Vice Grand Presidents. Sylvester, J.H., 1931-1940 (Box 476, Folder 23)
    - Monthly Reports. Vice Grand Presidents. Hall, F.H., 1931-1935 (Box 476, Folder 24)
    - Monthly Reports. Vice Grand Presidents, 1926 (Box 476, Folder 25)
    - Monthly Reports. Vice Grand Presidents, 1925 (Box 476, Folder 26)
    - Monthly Reports. Vice Grand Presidents, 1922-1929 (Box 476, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 297-6 (a). Grand Lodge Officers
    - Offices, Office Help, and Furniture, 1948-1955 (Box 476, Folder 28)
      August 1948-55.
    - Offices, Office Help, and Furniture, 1933-1948 (Box 476, Folder 29)
      1933-July 1948.
  - Sub-Series 297-7. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Moving Expenses, 1925 (Box 477, Folder 1)
    - Moving Expenses, 1922 (Box 477, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 297-8. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Grand Lodge Officers, 1929-1931 (Box 477, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 297-9. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Assistants to Vice Grand Presidents, 1924 (Box 477, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 297-10. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Grand Secretary-Treasurer's Office, 1924-1958 (Box 477, Folder 5)
      1924-May 20, 1958.
  - Sub-Series 297-12. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Charges Filed By Four Members of Lodge No. 20, Union Station Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1925 (Box 477, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 297-13. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Bonds, 1925-1957 (Box 477, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 297-14. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Research Director. Monthly Reports, 1928-1934 (Box 477, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 297-15. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Editor, The Railway Clerk, 1926 (Box 477, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 297-16. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Salaries, 1933-1963 (Box 477, Folder 10)
    - Salaries, 1928-1931 (Box 477, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 297-17. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Charges by Boston and Maine System Board of Adjustment, 1927-1928 (Box 477, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 297-18. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Daily Reports. General Representatives and Grand Lodge Organizers, 1957-1963 (Box 477, Folder 13)
    - Daily Reports. General Representatives and Grand Lodge Organizers, 1947-1956 (Box 477, Folder 14)
    - Weekly Reports. Grand Lodge Organizers, 1933-1947 (Box 477, Folder 15)
    - Daily Reports. General Representatives and Grand Lodge Organizers, 1945-1946 (Box 477, Folder 16)
    - Daily Reports. General Representatives and Grand Lodge Organizers. McCall, J.W., 1946 (Box 477, Folder 17)
    - Daily Reports. General Representatives and Grand Lodge Organizers. Mayberry, R.M., 1948 (Box 477, Folder 18)
      July-December 1948.
    - Daily Reports. General Representatives and Grand Lodge Organizers, 1930 (Box 477, Folder 19)
    - Daily Reports. General Representatives and Grand Lodge Organizers, 1929-1931 (Box 477, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 297-19. Grand Lodge Officers
    - General Representatives. Leaves of Absence, 1930 (Box 477, Folder 21)
    - Organizers. Leaves of Absence, 1935 (Box 477, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 297-20. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Vacations. General Representatives, 1929-1932 (Box 477, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 297-21. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Charges by Latour, F.E., Express Employee, Syracuse, New York, 1930 (Box 477, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 297-22. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Charges by Turner, T.J., President, Cleveland Expressmen's Lodge, Cleveland, Ohio, 1931 (Box 477, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 297-23. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Reports. Special Assistant to the Grand President, 1932 (Box 477, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 297-24. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Employment Record. General Representatives, 1932 (Box 477, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 297-25. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Grand Lodge Organizers, 1933-1946 (Box 477, Folder 28)
    - Grand Lodge Organizers, 1920 (Box 477, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 297-26. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Death. Levi, G.S., Grand Secretary-Treasurer, 1934-1937 (Box 477, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 297-27. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Research Director. Request for Leave of Absence, 1934-1935 (Box 477, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 297-28. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Research Department, 1947-1959 (Box 478, Folder 1)
      March 1947-January 29, 1959.
    - Research Department, 1935-1947 (Box 478, Folder 2)
      1935-February 1947.
  - Sub-Series 297-29. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Death. Fisher, R.E., Former Grand Secretary-Treasurer, and Wife, 1936-1937 (Box 478, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 297-30. Grand Lodge Officers
    - General Representatives. General; Barber, H.; Crawford, W.M.; Erickson, L.M.; Grosser, F.W., 1940-1957 (Box 478, Folder 4)
    - General Representatives. Herbst, C.A.; Kief, C.E.; McCarthy, R.J.; McKinney, L.; Reynolds, F.V.; Trembley, M.M., 1940-1953 (Box 478, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 297-31. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Assignment. Grand Lodge Organizers. O'Connell, J.J.; Perrott, D.H.; Platt, J.B.; Plecas, W.J.; Preston, J.R.; Pulliam, C.E.; Rapoport, W.; Ratcliffe, J.J.; Ripp, H.J.; Rogers, E.; Rugen, J.; Ryan, W.D.; Sando, E.O.; Scott, C.; Selkirk, J.L.; Smith, E.A., 1933-1954 (Box 478, Folder 6)
    - Assignment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Strahorn, M.C.; St. John, A.R.; Taylor, R.A.; Thornton, J.H.; Trembley, M.M.; Walmer, G.B.; Williams, A.; Williamson, W.; Youngberg, A.B., 1941-1949 (Box 478, Folder 7)
    - Employment. General Representatives, 1932 (Box 478, Folder 8)
    - Assignment. Grand Lodge Organizers. General, 1933-1940 (Box 478, Folder 9)
    - Assignment. General Representatives, 1925-1928 (Box 478, Folder 10)
    - Assignment. General Representatives, 1921-1922 (Box 478, Folder 11)
    - Assignment. Grand Lodge Organizers. General, 1947-1955 (Box 478, Folder 12)
    - Assignment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Bruen, F.; Campbell, D.K.; Clancy, P.T., 1929-1957 (Box 478, Folder 13)
    - Assignment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Clark, J.O.; Courtney, E.; Day, P.F.; Dickinson, W.J., 1940-1957 (Box 479, Folder 1)
    - Assignment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Gibson, G.W.; Giroux, C.A., 1939-1957 (Box 479, Folder 2)
    - Assignment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Goodwin, H.L.; Grimes, T.D.; Harrison, H.C.; Kelly, E.F., 1934-1957 (Box 479, Folder 3)
    - Assignment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Lanza, E.A.; Mayberry, R.M.; Mose, A.; Murphy, W.B., 1937-1957 (Box 479, Folder 4)
    - Assignment. Grand Lodge Organizers. McCarthy, F.E.; McKinney, L., 1938-1957 (Box 479, Folder 5)
    - Assignment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Roers, E.L., 1937-1957 (Box 479, Folder 6)
    - Assignment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Sommerfield, C.P.; Summerville, F.J.; Sylvester, L.H., 1946-1958 (Box 479, Folder 7)
    - Assignment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Tait, W.A.; Turner, W.J.; Tuttle, H.L., 1939-1957 (Box 479, Folder 8)
    - Assignment. Grand Lodge Organizers. General, 1929-1946 (Box 479, Folder 9)
    - Assignment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Abbott, J.R.; Aldrich, R.D.; Arnold, A.M., 1933-1949 (Box 479, Folder 10)
    - Assignment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Baldwin, H.F.; Bassewier, W.N.; Bier, C.; Boaz, V.L.; Bonham, R.S.; Bowe, D.S.; Brouner, F.B., 1940-1949 (Box 479, Folder 11)
    - Assignment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Davenport, N.W.; Davis, C.G.; Davis, R.E.; Dee, R.P.; Derrick, T.E.; Dolan, J.T.; Dunn, A.J.; Eastty, G.W.; Edwards, P.G., 1941-1949 (Box 479, Folder 12)
    - Assignment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Fitzpatrick, W.E.; Gifford, B.E.; Gilbert, J.I.; Grosser, F.W.; Gustafson, A.L., 1941-1949 (Box 479, Folder 13)
    - Assignment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Haines, J.B.; Harvey, A.P.; Herbst, C.A.; Hieber, F.; Hinkley, L.T.; Hodges, W.R.; Hughes, R.S.; Huntington, G.R., 1933-1949 (Box 479, Folder 14)
    - Assignment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Kief, C.E.; Kleist, R.D.; Larson, A.E.; Lawler, J.F.; Lennon, A.L.; Lucado, F.D.; McAllister, C.A.; McCall, J.W.; McGhee, A.J.; McGuigan, J.C.; McIlvaine, J.; McLeroy, J.H.; McTigue, H.; Madison, T.L.; Mashburn, W.K.; M, 1941-1949 (Box 479, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 297-32. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Babcock, R.A.; Blackwell, A.; Bruen, F.; Byrnes, W.S.; Crawford, W.M.; Courtney, E.; Day, P.F.; Dunaway, H.P.; Goodwin, H.L., 1953-1958 (Box 480, Folder 1)
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Grimes, T.D.; Harrison, H.C.; Murphy, W.B.; Perrott, D.; Sommerfield, C.F.; Summerville, F.J.; Sylvester, L.H.; Turner, W.J.; Wilson, E.J., 1953-1958 (Box 480, Folder 2)
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Turner, W.J. Subject: "Appeal", 1957-1958 (Box 480, Folder 3)
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Abbott, J.R.- Arnold, A.M., 1936-1949 (Box 480, Folder 4)
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Badsley, R.- Bux, A.J., 1936-1949 (Box 480, Folder 5)
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Carr, M.S.- Crowe, R.H., 1936-1949 (Box 480, Folder 6)
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Dalsky, A.J.- Freeborn, W., 1936-1949 (Box 480, Folder 7)
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Gaither, J.H.- Gustafson, A.L., 1936-1949 (Box 480, Folder 8)
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Harvey, A.P.- Huntington, G.R., 1936-1949 (Box 480, Folder 9)
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Jeannette, H.B.- Lyons, B.J., 1936-1949 (Box 480, Folder 10)
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Madison, P.L.- Murphy, H.R., 1936-1949 (Box 480, Folder 11)
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. McAllister, C.A.- McMillan, E.A., 1936-1949 (Box 480, Folder 12)
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Nelesen, J.J.- Queen, G.M., 1936-1949 (Box 480, Folder 13)